[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_22||(99_MSQ_23\u0026\u0026!99_MSQ_35)",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Darkness in the Brightwood",
        "Description": "Yonas recalls a priest named Brother Umberto who once ministered to the Soulwardens. The two of you decide to seek out Umberto in the town of Walsham in Brightwood and learn his fate.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need to recruit more Soulwardens.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, we must find allies as well. We needn't repeat the failed experiment of doing this alone.\\n\\nSuch fools we were, to turn away those who sought to support us.",
        "InProgressResponse": "There is no more for us here. Meet me at the Shadowmine Shrine.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "It appears the town fell to the Lost primarily from within, no signs of any defense.\\n\\nI wonder if Brother Umberto sought aid from somewhere else.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Shining Knight",
        "Description": "On the trail of Brother Umberto, you and Yonas have decided to head west, where the priest apparently went to request assistance from the knight, Ser Galahad.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What happened to the king?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Hm. Some say King Artorius fell during the war, others say he fled, and there were even whispers that he turned.\\n\\nPerhaps Galahad can shed light on the fates of both the king and Brother Umberto.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Go on your way then, young Soulwarden. I will be along soon enough.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I welcome your aid for Umberto's sake, but I did not realize you were a Soulwarden.\\n\\nDuring the Wars, your order insisted on the delusion that the Crimson Madness could not be defeated. Your friend, Yonas, now claims it's returned.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p5",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Losing the Faith",
        "Description": "Investigate Staudt's Manor and Kalterstein Cemetery for more clues about Umberto and then meet Galahad and Yonas at the shrine to the north.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Did you find any clues?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Nothing to explain how this entire region fell to the Lost… just horrific stories as so many succumbed to despair.\\n\\nThere is evidence Umberto and the Vigil abandoned this place, but no indication where they went.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Go on then. We both have a duty to perform.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I feel guilty saying it, but I am relieved to see the knight depart. He clings to his ignorance with unwavering assurance.\\n\\nThe Corrupted are here in force, just as I suspected. This level-headed ranger has confirmed it.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p5",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Losing the Faith",
        "Description": "Investigate Staudt's Manor and Kalterstein Cemetery for more clues about Umberto and then meet Galahad and Yonas at the shrine to the north.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Did you find any clues?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Nothing to explain how this entire region fell to the Lost… just horrific stories as so many succumbed to despair.\\n\\nThere is evidence Umberto and the Vigil abandoned this place, but no indication where they went.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Go on then. We both have a duty to perform.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I feel guilty saying it, but I am relieved to see the knight depart. He clings to his ignorance with unwavering assurance.\\n\\nThe Corrupted are here in force, just as I suspected. This level-headed ranger has confirmed it.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Crimson Menace",
        "Description": "Yonas has discovered that the Corrupted have claimed several resource locations in Brightwood, including a massive iron mine. You need to investigate if they have an ulterior motive in seizing the mine and then meet Yonas in the town of Calvary.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What are the Corrupted after?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That is what you must investigate. I suggest you start in the mine. It could very well be something buried here.\\n\\nFind out what the Corrupted are seeking, and then meet me in the town of Calvary to the east.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Go on. I will meet you in the town of Calvary.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I was on the verge of going to search for you… to apologize. I doubted both you and the old man, but I was wrong.\\n\\nOn the way to Caer Dun, I witnessed firsthand the size and activity of the Corrupted forces here in the Brightwood.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 31,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Gates of Great Cleave",
        "Description": "Yonas is scouting out the Corrupted presence in Great Cleave where he has asked that you join him and formulate a strategy for driving the enemy out of Brightwood.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where is Yonas now?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The old man has more courage than good sense - he's gone to ascertain whether the Corrupted have a presence in Great Cleave.\\n\\nI urged him to wait, but he refused. I suggest you head north right away to ensure his safety.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Be wary out there, my friend. It seems nowhere outside these town walls is truly safe.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I saw Yonas in the tavern - he's recruiting new Soulwardens and entertaining some dream of claiming Caer Dun for the Order.\\n\\nBalmy as ever, but I'm glad he's back behind town walls. Good work.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Vigil’s Truth",
        "Description": "Galahad has reached an impasse in the investigation into what happened to Umberto and the Bright Vigil. It's decided that you will speak with Mayor Pennyfather and follow up on any hints he's willing to share.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Have you asked Mayor Pennyfather?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I did speak with the Mayor…  a bit nervous that one. Are you suggesting he's hiding something from me?\\n\\nHm, I suppose I'm not the best conversationalist. Perhaps you should speak with him. Go on.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you learn anything definitive about Umberto, make sure to let me know.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Greetings, young Warden. I understand you left town after speaking with Pennyfather.\\n\\nI must ask - what did you learn? Is it true that the Vigil resorted to dark methods of battling the Lost menace?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Sun_p2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Betrayal at Brightrest",
        "Description": "Mayor Tunstall Pennyfather admitted that he was aware of the Bright Vigil's atrocities and the curse that followed. After discussing with Galahad and the Master Alchemist Sun Fuchun, it becomes clear where the trail leads next.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, the Master Alchemist Sun Fuchun.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Very well, then I will leave you to follow the trail wherever it leads.\\n\\nI will attempt to learn more about Umberto's fall… I've begun to wonder if he ever sought to find the source of the Lost plague.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If everything Pennyfather says is true, Umberto has horrific crimes to answer for…\\n\\nUnless he too has fallen Lost.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, you got the Bright Sigils? Amazing. I can't express how good it feels to have an ally in this effort - especially one who can fight!\\n\\nWe'll need some token from the Grand Vigilant as well,  but that can wait.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Azoth Tree",
        "Description": "In order to cleanse the curse from Caer Dun, Sun Fuchun needs Sacred Waters collected from the Azoth Tree in the nearby grove, but it's necessary to acquire vessels from the Shamans in the neighboring caverns in order to extract the waters. After collecting the waters, rejoin Sun Fuchun.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The Angry Earth?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, but I'm not so keen on that wording. The so-called \"Angry Earth\" evolved from a deep and primal power.\\n\\nThey pose a grave threat to humanity, but their bond with the energy of azoth is sacred.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The tree is invested with vast power. Step lightly in the grove.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The alchemist is clearly gifted in some vestal fashion - you've done well partnering with her.\\n\\nMy tidings are less inspiring… no sign of \"Grand Vigilant\" Umberto in the Fen, but a clue guided me to find him back here.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Umberto’s Sentence",
        "Description": "Galahad has tracked Umberto to Vigil's Stand and it's now time to confront the fallen priest, acquire his Heartgem and then rejoin Galahad at the Postrekhin Shrine.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"He forged himself a Heartgem.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Did he? I will refrain from commenting on that practice out of respect, but Umberto must be called to answer for his crimes.\\n\\nIf the Heartgem protects him, it must be destroyed, though I cannot be the one to do it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You're a brave soul to undertake this endeavor. Umberto has become a monster.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "It is done, then? The tragic tale of the once-brave Brother Umberto finally draws to a close.\\n\\nI am grateful to you, my friend, for helping me atone for my part in all this. We will never know if I might've prevented these atrocities.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 34,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p9",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Curse of Caer Dun",
        "Description": "Working with Ser Galahad, you've defeated Grand Vigilant Umberto and taken his Heartgem. All that remains is to return to Caer Dun and follow Sun Fuchun's instructions for removing the curse.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What will you do?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I will return to Calvary and seek other ways I can help restore the Brightwood.\\n\\nPerhaps Pennyfather will have grown a spine by now. Either way, I will find some way to serve.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I will give your offer due consideration, my friend. Until then, good fortune to you at Caer Dun.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've done well, young one. As menacing as that Corrupted army in Great Cleave may be, I believe we are safe here.\\n\\nI will maintain my focus on recruiting and training new Soulwardens to defend the place.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 34,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p9",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Curse of Caer Dun",
        "Description": "Working with Ser Galahad, you've defeated Grand Vigilant Umberto and taken his Heartgem. All that remains is to return to Caer Dun and follow Sun Fuchun's instructions for removing the curse.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What will you do?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I will return to Calvary and seek other ways I can help restore the Brightwood.\\n\\nPerhaps Pennyfather will have grown a spine by now. Either way, I will find some way to serve.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I will give your offer due consideration, my friend. Until then, good fortune to you at Caer Dun.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've done well, young one. As menacing as that Corrupted army in Great Cleave may be, I believe we are safe here.\\n\\nI will maintain my focus on recruiting and training new Soulwardens to defend the place.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 34,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p8",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Corpse Crone",
        "Description": "Following the vision you received from the Azoth Tree, you've decided to search for the sorceress with the purple eye. You must revisit Mayor Tunstall Pennyfather in Calvary and then meet Galahad on the road to Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What does that mean?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It means you have been imbued with a power that exceeds my understanding, and it makes you both a target and a threat to the enemy.\\n\\nI do not envy the destiny that lies before you, nor do I know where it leads.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I believe in you, and if you need me, I will be here.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've heard Pennyfather's sordid tale, have you? I do not give that man's story much credence.\\n\\nNeither do I have any desire to meet this sorceress… such types cannot be trusted, in my experience.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
